http://www.cu-portland.edu/privacy

HomePrivacy Statement
Explore this section
Closure
Privacy Statement
Concordia University Portland has a firm commitment to privacy. The following statement addresses the information-gathering and dissemination practices for the Concordia University website.
Personal Information
Concordia University Portland collects personal information that is voluntarily provided or obtained within the parameters of anti-spam laws (e.g., name, address, email or telephone number), unless you voluntarily provide it to us by sending email, participating in a survey or completing an online form. Concordia University Portland may collect this data at any and all opportunities. We value the privacy of our students, alums, friends and donors. We honor requests for removal from receiving correspondence. Concordia University Portland does not share any personal information with third parties.
When you visit our website, we automatically collect certain information, such as:
Domain, country, IP address
Browser, platform, resolution
Entrance-Exit Pages, Pages Visited, Referrals
Date, Time
Search Terms and Search Engines
This is standard practice for websites, and is not used for any purpose other than to evaluate how we can design the site to best serve your needs. none of that information is personally identifiable, or matched to any data collected in a form.
In order to provide better and more secure service we will occasionally use a "cookie." A cookie is a small piece of information stored on your computer that can uniquely identify your browser, and may include other information about your visit to the site. The cookie cannot be read by a Web site other than the one that set the cookie.
Security
Concordia University Portland complies with all statutory and legal requirements with respect to access to information. Concordia-owned websites have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. User and password information is encrypted before it is transmitted across the network.
Links to External Sites
This site contains links to external, non-Concordia sites. Concordia University Portland is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.
Read More
Read Less
Explore this section
Admission
